It happened while your comment was given the appointment letter,
talk about the President's policy,
so in today's video we will share all your
information, so become Ramesh,
watch the video, enter it and if you had visited
Chanchal,
subscribe to the channel and definitely click on the notification light,
then here it
gets a message as per your questions,
on the topic of instruction water, first of all
I am yours, two committees shy and you are
seeing this real, this plan is
from ICICI Lombard, it is so
complete, if we talk about ICICI Lombard
Personal Product Polygraph Test, then
people from 18 years to 80 years
can take this plan, as an individual and
family doctor, you will be
able to see this plan, and if you work as a family doctor for
different children, this is
fz25, let's talk about
what is covered in this plan and
what is not covered, see the explanation is
even stronger, if you were to do any such
activity, in case of suicide, there will be
no claim under the quality  If
Owaisi does any activity, which I have already
mentioned in the video of health insurance, the link of which you will
find in the description, then also you will
not get the film, but the good thing is that
inside the plant, even if you are outside India and you have an accident
here, even if you have a
problem with this
polythene like for your bike, then in
this way
you will get the claim here also. Now when it comes to
what things do we get to know about inside this plant,
personal
accidental, there is up to dead quantum, if
any code number gets melted, that means someone gets a
lens loss, their house gets damaged, then that
too will be covered,
you will get cover for this permanent disability also because
this is Bedi's extra dental care policy,
after that when you take this plan, there is
no need for any medical examination,
people between the age of 18 to 31 years can take
this plan, then there is no need for
pre-existing and medical
examination in it, now while talking about the
checkpoint which I understood.  Code you will be able to know
how to avail the option benefit
2. Within your benefits,
accidental hospitalization benefit second
week accidental hospitalization didi
alarm it's ok jokes alarms that you get, you
know how much it is, the first
option is you had a free leg in it, if you
choose the option of Tilak understanding in it, then
you will get cover of 210 rupees in accidental hospitalization
and the accident
hospital digital logic will be up to ₹1000,
so the second option comes of ₹500
spoon dry ginger, in that you have update,
when you saw accidental hospitalization ₹2500000 packet and whatever Julia Roberts will give for
hospitalization, it will remain the same,
according to the day, now after this the third and fourth
option is traction 15x, here you will get only ₹50 for
accidental hospitalization
and the Devi alarms, you will
get only ₹1, so that comes after that  This
is your 2625, understand on the other side, in this you will get a valid
accident hospitalization of up to ₹1,
try and in this you will be able to get it
only till 2030, you need an app, your
support should be of the article, half a spoon and fitting,
next question you understand, it is
electronic, that 25dec and accidental
hospital today price, that ₹2000 will be available here, if we
talk about the policy term, then
three years, one year and favorite option is
available inside the plant to see at night,
you can also see these lines online and
I will get you the field worker period of fifteen countries,
okay now see, it is a very
simple thing, if it is an accidental policy, then
you have to pay the premium clearly, then there will be
ginger in it, it is another thing
that there is no rocket science in the option, if you
do it comfortably then there is a point for 61010,
okay now see, if you see anyone,
what will be the answer documentation, see it
on your skin or
Muzaffarnagar eligibility and their solution,
read Tanu now  Imagine if a person becomes a
student in that chapter, will
his family be there in this condition, after
completing all these formalities
you have to inform the
world, in this you have to
tell the company all the things, it happens that
people become so soft that they
live in a different state of mind, that is why
I always say that whenever people buy an
insurance product in this manner, go to an
insurance advisor whom you
know personally and maintain a good relationship,
in today's time, most of the
people are misled because when those
insurance advisors request you, they make the
same mistake in the beginning, they
put their greed first, please
take an insurance policy also and you will
get the option here, stop this thing otherwise you
people will keep abusing such programs on the internet, on the
basis of my experience, till date maximum number of
questions come on our channel, maximum number of this is about
English personality, I will reply to you, okay,
except for all the maximum number of specialties Mukesh, so I am a
practical best thing  Do it, that's why brother, do
not understand the value of your Jhajjar,
choose a person who would have been the right mark, I
want to tell you everything, I will tell you everything,
but now let's start putting you in the beginning, if this happens then this is what
I wanted to say, it's a
joke, many people might have felt
bad about this, but I have to tell the truth, so if you meet the
public then I will meet you
in a free video, but before leaving I
would like to remind you one thing, insurance, a protection
home production, should never be taken incomplete,
you can cross check all the information,
but first of all watch this dance video,
after that go to the description,
you will get the link in the reception, by clicking there you
can see all the information that I told you, whatever I
tell you on the skin because
that will also become your prostate, thank you so
much you asked the question and watched the video till the end